
> - Do you really want to delete the info for this baby?
Вы уверены, что хотите удалить информацию (or инфо) об этом малыше

> - In this screen the lucky number and period corresponding to the
> firstname and the zodiacal sign and period corresponding to the birthdate
> are displayed
В этом окне показаны: счастливое число, соответствующее имени, знаку зодиака и
счастливый период, соответствующий дате рождения

> - You need at least Palm OS 3.5 to run this application
Для запуска программы Вам необходима Palm OS версии 3.5 или выше

> - Babies information administration
Администрирование информации о малышах

> - Weight and Height follow up during the 3 first years
Вес и рост малыша в развитии до 3-х лет

> - Visual check with the average values
Визуальная оценка по средним значениям

> - List of the first words
Список первых слов

> - List of the first actions
Список первых действий

> - Vaccinations checklist
Контрольный список прививок

> - Zodiacal sign and period
Зодиакальный знак и период

> - Firstname symbolic (lucky number, lucky period)
Символы имени (счастливый номер и период)

> - the (for a date, ex the 25 March 2003)
It is not used. Date example:  19 января 2003, 25 февраля 2003, марта, апреля, мая,
июня, июля, августа, сентября, октября, ноября, декабря.

> - for (when extracting to the Memo you have Babycheck for .....)
для

